remository.com 2019-03-06

# Remository Software Privacy Policy

 | 

**Remository Software Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy applies to the website of Remository Software.

| To contact our organization, use the following information.  
---  
 | Remository Software  
service@remository.com  
  
Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we disclose all of the information we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with the it.

Information is collected for the following purposes.  
---  
 | Completing an activity or transaction  
Website and system administration  
Research and Development  
Contact users for marketing  
The following organizations have access to the information we collect.  
---  
 | Ourselves  
  
If you are concerned about your personal information we collect, contact us using the information contained in this policy.

Our web site uses cookies to enhance how it operates and ensure we better serve our visitors.

Our servers automatically collect logs that may record statistical information such as visitors' IP addresses, type of operating systems, time of visit, web pages requested, etc., and identify categories of visitors by items such as domains and browser types. These usage statistics are are used to improve our websites and maintain site security.

The website collects the following types of information.  
---  
 | Information about an individual's characteristics  
Web site issued unique identifiers  
Current physical location information  
Web Navigation information  
Computer system information  
  
If you have a question about our privacy policy, or you would like to dispute any information collected contact us using the information contained in this policy.
